Sean Hufnagel

Full Stack Developer

Sean.Hufnagel@Ibotta.com | Denver, Colorado 80223 | (720) 697-0289 github.com/swhufnagel | swhufnagel.github.io/PortfolioUpdate | linkedin.com/in/sean-hufnagel-38a888125

Summary

User-focused full stack web-developer that specializes in Javascript. Effective at combining creativity and problem solving to develop user-friendly applications. My optimistic spirit drives the whole team to excel and perform without hesitation, I strive to succeed with no alternative.

Technical Skills

Languages: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS, etc.

Applications: Visual Studio Code, Atom, MySQLWorkbench, Photoshop, Illustrator, Gimp, etc.

Projects

Tunedea | Code | App

- Summary: Generates song suggestions based on the user selected artist using multiple Spotify APIs
- Responsibilities: Design front-end and display results rendered from Spotify
- Tools: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Spotify Search API, Spotify Seed API, Semantic.css, OAuth

Experience

Ibotta Inc. Denver, CO November 2016 - Present

Care Agent

- Worked in 4 different departments from Online Shopping to Customer Fraud
- Recognized for 100% score on Quality Assessments
- Became point of contact for newer agents that need assistance

Grande's Italiano Jupiter, FL January 2014 - June 2016

Server/Trainer

- Recognized for performance and promoted to Trainer
- Highest sales on serving team

Datastrip Inc. Shelton, CT October 2012 - November 2013

Intern

- Offered a raise for working quickly and efficiently while testing units
- Recognized for

Education

University of Denver Denver, Colorado August 2019

Certificate from Coding Bootcamp

Palm Beach State College Palm Beach Gardens, Florida May 2016

Associate's Degree in Computer Programming

Pomperaug High School Southbury, Connecticut June 2010

High School Diploma

References are available upon request.